【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第01集
罗斯的新女友 The One With Ross' New Girlfriend
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：小龟快快跑
来自北京的457号航班 已经抵达
Flight number 457 from Beijing now arriving.
哦 我的天
Oh my God!
哦 我的天啊
对不起 让开 让开 有急事 拜托
Oh, my. Excuse me. Move, move, move! Emergency, please!
对不起 对不起
Excuse me, excuse me.
瑞秋
Rach!
总算找到你了
There you are!
嘿      嗨
Hey!         Hi!
噢 那么 那么
Oh! So, so...
在中国还好吗 老兄
How was China? You!
很棒啊 怎么了      什么
It was, it was great. Oh, what happened?        What?
你在流血      是吗
You're bleeding.        I am?
天啊      哦 看看  我真的在流血
God!         Oh, look at that! Yes, I am.
还是别管我了 别管我了
Anyway, enough about me, enough about me.
这位从东方归来的先生
Mr. Back From The Orient!
快  我要听所有的事 要一字不漏
Come on, I wanna hear everything. Everything!
我该从哪儿开始呢
Well, where do I start?
这位是茱莉 茱莉 这位是瑞秋
Well, this is Julie. Julie, this is Rachel.
你好
Hi!
这束花是      噢
Oh! These are...        Oh!
这束花不是送你的
These are...aren't for you.
是要送给你的
These are for you.
欢迎造访我国
Welcome to our country.
谢谢你 我是纽约人
Thank you. I'm from New York.
没关系 用来止血刚好
Well, not a problem. We'll just use them to stop the bleeding.
好 去领行李了吗
Okay. Baggage claim?
好      好
Okay         Okay
不可能
No way.
她去机场了
I'm telling you, she went to the airport.
她要去对罗斯表白了
And she's gonna go for it with Ross.
哇 我的天啊 这是大事
Oh, my God. This is huge. This...
这比大事还大 这简直是
This is bigger than huge. This is like...
好吧 什么比大事还大
All right, what's bigger than huge?
这件事      没错
This?        Yes.
你们弄了个新发型
Guys, you got new haircuts!
是呀 没错 多亏了这位美发大师菲比沙宣
Yes, yes, we did. Thanks to Vidal Buffay.
因为 我们的光彩来自您的风(沙宣广告词)
Because, you know, "If you don't look good, we don't look good."
我爱死那个声音了
I love that voice!
你们大家      喔 瑞秋
You guys!         Oh! Oh! Rachel!
机场 机场 罗斯 不是一个人
Airport, airport. Ross. Not, not alone.
茱莉 搂着她
Julie. Julie. Arm around her!
抽筋 抽筋 抽筋
Cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
我想她可能是想表达什么
Okay, I think she's trying to tell us something.
快 快找出句子的动词
Quick, get the verbs.
你 你
You! You!
你说他喜欢我 你 你
You said he liked me! You! You
你们这两个慢半拍的
You slowpokes!
没错 行李全在我们手上
That's all right, Rach. We got the bags.
嗨 你好
Hi. Hello.
茱莉 她是我妹妹摩妮卡 他是钱德
Julie, this is my sister, Monica. This is Chandler.
嘿      菲比 嗨
Hey.         Phoebe. Hi.
乔伊 你还好吗      你好
Joey, what up?         Hey.
大家注意 这位是茱莉      茉莉
Everyone, this is Julie.         Julie.
噢喔
Oh!
嗨
Hi!
嗨 就当我不在这儿 我们根本没见过面
Hi! But I'm not here, you haven't met me.
等明天 我没有坐20个小时的飞机
I'll make a much better first impression tomorrow
留给你们的印象会好很多
when I don't have 20 hours of cab and plane on me.
还有巴士      哦 我的天
And bus.         Oh my God!
那个尖叫的家伙      还有吐口水的人
With the screaming guy.        And the spitting...
你们一定得听听这个故事
You gotta hear this story.
我们坐了一辆有200年之久的巴士
We're on this bus that's easily 200 years old.
最少200年
Easy two hundred, at least.
有个家伙      后来鸡在她大腿上大便了
And this guy...        And the chicken poops in her lap!
真是对不起
Oh, I'm so sorry.
我把结局说出来了 是吗
I just gave away the ending, didn't I?
我刚刚在计程车上 听过这个故事
I just heard this story in the cab.
然后我就再也忘不了
And it is all I can think about.
太令人意外了 怎么会这样子的呢
This is amazing. I mean, how? How did this happen?
我们一起读的研究生
Ross and I were in grad school together
毕业后就没见过面了
But we haven't seen each other since then.
我一到中国 你们猜 负责勘探的人是谁
Well, I land in China, guess who's in charge of the dig?
茱莉
Julie!
这不是太妙了吗
Julie. Isn't that great?
真是妙得让人想踹你一脚
I mean, isn't that just kick you in the crotch,
再对着你的脖子吐口水
spit on your neck fantastic?
只是一种形容的方式
It's an expression.
我们只是过来打声招呼
We just wanted to say a quick hi.
然后我们就要去看宝宝
Then we're gonna go see the baby.
然后睡一觉
Then we've gotta get some sleep.
我们现在的时间 其实是明晚六点钟
Yeah, it's really 6 o'clock tomorrow night, our time.
好 千万别告诉我明天会怎样
Okay well, listen, don't tell us what's gonna happen though.
因为我喜欢惊喜
'cause I like to be surprised.
再见      再见
Bye!        Bye!
嘿 瑞秋 可以给我来点咖啡吗
Hey, Rach. Can I get some coffee?
当然好      谢谢
Yeah, Sure.        Thank you!
嗨 瑞秋      你跟他说了没
Hey, Rach.        Did you talk to him yet?
没      那就别想喝
No.        Then, no.
你在中国到底发生什么事了
So, what the hell happened to you in China?
上回我们离开这里的时候 你还爱着
I mean, when last we left you, you were totally in love with, you know.
我知道 曾经是那样没错
I know. I know I was.
可是我心中一直有个声音 在提醒我
But there was always this little voice inside that kept saying:
那是不可能的 你要往前走
"It's never gonna happen. Move on."
你知道那是谁的声音吧
You know whose voice that was?
上帝吗
God?
是你啊 老兄
It was you, pal.
也许是上帝在模仿我
Well, maybe it was God doing me.
你说得没错
Look, you were right. Okay?
在她眼里我只是一个朋友
She looks at me and sees a friend. That's all.
然后我就遇到茱莉
And then I met Julie and...
我们在一起非常开心
I don't know. We're having a great time.
我必须得说 要不是你的话
And I have to say, I never would have gone for it with her,
我绝对不可能跟她在一起的
if it hadn't been for you.
你欠我一个大人情  大个子
Well, you owe me one, big guy.
你的柠檬汁来了
Here's your lemonade.
我没叫柠檬汁
I didn't order lemonade.
那就退回去
Oh, well, then you better go take that back.
不然他们会找你收钱的
'Cause they're gonna charge you for that.
但是      快 快 快 快点 快点
But        Go, go, go! Come on, come on!
好了 你了解到了什么
Okay, so, what did you find out?
他说
He said...
他说他们在一起非常开心 我很抱歉
He said they're having a great time. I'm sorry.
什么
What?
不过 只要你愿意看 这也有好的一面
But the silver lining, if you wanna see it,
这完全是他自己的决定
is that he made this decision all by himself,
绝对没有任何外来力量的协助
without any outside help whatsoever.
这哪里是好的一面
How is that a silver lining?
你要非常愿意 才能看得出来
You have to really wanna see it.
讽刺的是 这些家伙都是 上体育课时没人愿意挑的
Ironically, these are the guys who were picked last in gym.
嘿 菲比
Hey, Pheebs.
知道我在想什么吗      哦 可以
You know what I'm thinking?         Oh, okay.
在想
How...
你很久没跟人嘿咻了
it's been so long since you've had sex.
所以你在想 现在有没有什么新花招
you're wondering if they've changed it?
不是 不过现在 我真的在想这件事了
No. Although now that's what I'm thinking.
好吧 那你刚才在想什么
All right. So, what were you thinking?
你帮他们剪了很不错的发型
Well, I was thinking that you gave the guys suchvgreat haircuts.
我想 或许你也可以帮我剪
So, I thought maybe you'd like to do mine.
哦 不行
Oh! No.
有什么不行      因为我只是
Why not?         Because I'm just...
我非常挑剔 而且是个控制狂
I'm incredibly anal and an unbelievable control freak.
不 你不是      我知道我不是 不过你是
No, you're not.        I know I'm not, but you are.
我只是不想伤害你的感情
I was trying to spare your feelings.
喂 哦 你好
Hello? Oh, hi.
好 等一下 罗斯 茱莉找你
Yeah, hold on a second. Ross, Julie for you.
喂 嘿
Hello? Hi.
嘿 有人认识什么好裁缝吗
Hey. Anybody know a good tailor?
有衣服要修改吗      不是
You need clothes altered?         No no.
我只是想找个人 拿粉笔在我身上画画
I'm just looking for a man to draw on me with chalk.
去找法兰克
Why don't you go see Frankie.
我家的人一直找他做衣服
My family's been going to him forever.
我15岁时第一套西装就是他做的 不 等等 是16岁
He did my first suit when I was 15, no, wait, 16.
不 对不起 是15岁
No, excuse me, 15.
好吧 1990年 到底是什么时候
All right, when was 1990?
好吧 掏耳朵时只要棉签碰到东西就别继续挖了
Okay, you have to stop the QTip when there's resistance.
好 好的 甜心 我们等会儿见
Okay. Okay. Sweetheart, I'll see you later.
好的 拜 什么
Okay, bye. What?
喔 你真好
Oh, that is so sweet.
不
No.
好 不 你先挂
No. Okay. No, you hang up.
不 你先 好吧
No, you. Okay.
一 二 三
Okay. One, two, three.
你也没啊
Well you didn't hang up either.
她没挂掉      她没挂掉
She didn't hang up.        She didn't hang up.
好吧 不行
Okay, no.
不 你来挂电话
No, you hang up.
你 你
You. You. Yo...
对不起 我还以为你是在对我说
Sorry, I thought you were talking to me.
瑞秋      对不起
Rachel.        Sorry.
我再打给她      好吧
I'll just call her back.         Okay.
嗨 亲爱的 对不起 刚刚断线了
Hi, sweetie. I'm sorry. We got disconnected.
不 你挂
No, you hang up.
好吧 我怎么会这样
Okay, okay, okay. How did this happen to me?
我怎么会这样
How did this happen to me?
一个礼拜前 两个礼拜前 我还好好的
A week ago, two weeks ago, I was fine.
罗斯只是罗斯 就是一个家伙
Ross was just Ross. Just this guy.
如今 突然间 他是罗斯
Now all of a sudden, he's Ross
是我无福拥有的好家伙
this really great guy that I can't have.
以前我也希望你能拥有他
Sweetie, I wanted you to have him too.
我知道
I know you did.
我会熬过去的 我会熬过去的
I'm just gonna deal with it. I'm just gonna deal with it.
我得离开这里
I gotta get out of here!
我不管你们怎么说
Okay, I don't care what you guys say.
她真的有心事
Something's bothering her.
知道吗 我想当时我是16岁
You know, I think I was 16.
拜托 只要后面修一点点就好
Please, just a little bit off the back.
我还是不要
I'm still on "no".
早      嘿
Morning.         Hey.
你们可以先闭上眼睛吗
Do you guys think you could close your eyes for just a sec?
不 不 不 我不会再上你的当了
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not falling for that again.
怎么了
What's going on?
我昨晚做了一件傻事
Well, I sort of did a stupid thing last night.
什么傻事
What stupid thing did you do?
恶心
Ew!
巴洛 你去穿好衣服
Okay, Paulo, why don't you just go get dressed.
然后就可以走了 再见
And then you'll be on your way. Okay. Byebye.
瑞秋 怎么会这样
Rachel, how did this happen?
我也不知道 我昨晚碰巧遇到他了
I don't know, I kind of ran into him last night.
在哪里遇到的      他的公寓 这是果汁吗
Where?         At his apartment. Is this juice?
喂 不是因为他想勾引菲比 你才甩了他的吗
Whoa. And the fact that you dumped him because he hit on Phoebe?
哦 天啊 我知道 我真可悲 我是个没用的人
Oh, God, I know. I'm pathetic, I'm a loser.
你不可悲 你只是悲伤
Honey, you're not pathetic. You're just sad.
没错 伤心的人总是会做傻事的
Yeah. I mean, people do stupid things when they're upset.
天啊 如果每个我不该上床的人 都给我五分钱
My God! If I had a nickel for every guy I wish I hadn't...
我们现在谈的 是你犯下的大错
But this is about your horrible mistake.
嗨      嘿
Hi.        Hey
嗨      抱歉我们迟到了
Hi!        Sorry we're late.
我们刚刚在
We were...
哦 是跟触摸有关的
Well, there was touching.
嘿 罗斯      巴洛
Hey, Ross!         Paclo. Ha.
怎么
What a...
你怎么会在这里
What, what are you doing here?
我来上瑞秋      啊
I do Raquel.         Ah.
这么说他回来了
So, he's back?
对 他回来了 有问题吗
Yeah, he's back. Is that a problem?
不 没有问题
No, not a problem.
很好 很欣慰不构成问题
Good. Glad it's not a problem.
你不能再碰我的屁股
Okay, you're gonna have to not touch my ass.
尽管有美味的面包圈 还有一触即发的紧张局势
Well, despite the yummy bagels and palpable tension.
我还是得去改我的裤子
I've got pants that need to be altered.
嘿 钱德 看到法兰克的时候
Oh, hey, Chandler, when you see Frankie,
跟他说乔伊崔比亚尼问候他
tell him Joey Tribbiani says hello.
这样子他就会懂了
He'll know what it means.
你确定他能解开 如此深奥的谜题
You sure he's gonna be able to crack that code?
真好玩
You know, it's funny.
上次巴洛在这里的时候 我的头发还很短很可爱
The last time Paolo was here, my hair was so much shorter and cuter.
好吧 好吧
All right. Okay.
但你必须得保证
But, but you have to promise that
你不会管太多 太唠叨 还有别太摩妮卡就是了
you will not be all like controlly and bossy and all, you know, Monica about it.
我保证      好 我看看
I promise.        All right, let's see.
好 你们有些会被修剪 有些不会
Now, some of you are gonna get cut and some of you aren't.
不过我保证 你们全都不会感到痛楚
But I promise, none of you will feel a thing.
好
Okay.
够了 我不干了
All right, that's it. I quit.
干嘛 我什么都没说
What? I didn't say anything!
但这不是相信人的表情
Yeah, but this isn't the face of a person who trusts a person.
这种表情是
This is the face of a person who, you know...
不相信人的表情
doesn't trust a person.
我很抱歉 我很抱歉 菲比
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Phoebe.
只是这比我们讨论的发型要短多了
It's just a little shorter than what we had discussed.
你放轻松好吗 我知道自己在做什么
Would you relax? I know what I am doing.
这就是他的发型
This is how he wears it.
谁的发型      黛米摩尔
How who wears it?         Demi Moore.
黛米摩尔不是个男的
Demi Moore is not a he.
哦  他在"亚瑟"和"十全十美"里就是个男的
Well, he was a he in "Arthur" and in "10".
那个人是杜利摩尔
That's Dudley Moore!
我说的是 我要黛米摩尔的发型
I said I wanted it like Demi Moore!
哦 哦      哦 我的天啊
Oh. Oh!         Oh, my God!
哦 天啊      哦 我的天啊
Oh, God!         Oh, my God!
哦 我的天 我很抱歉 对不起
Oh, my God! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry！
黛米摩尔是哪一个啊
Which one is Demi Moore?
她是  "桃色机密" "不道德的交易"
She's the actress that was in "Disclosure", "Indecent Proposal",
"人鬼情未了"里的那个女星
"Indecent Proposal", "Ghost"!
她的发型很漂亮的
Oh, she's got gorgeous hair.
我知道      我的天啊
I know!         Oh, my God!
裤管的褶边要多长
How long do you want the cuffs?
要跟这件裤子的寿命一样长
At least as long as I have the pants.
我刚听懂
I just got that.
现在要量你的内侧长度
Okay. Now we'll do your inseam.
她的情况怎样
How is she?
现在还很难说
It's too soon to tell.
她在休息了 起码这是一个好现象
She's resting, which is a good sign.
头发的情况呢
How's the hair?
我不想骗你
I'm not gonna lie to you, Ross.
看起来不妙
It doesn't look good.
我夹起了一边的头发 似乎能阻止卷曲
I put a clip on one side, which seems to have stopped the curling.
我们可以去看她了吗
Can we see her?
你的发型看起来太棒了 反而会让她更难过
Your hair looks too good. I think it would upset her.
罗斯 你进去看看她吧
Ross, why don't you come on in.
你还好吗      我没事
Well, how you doing?         I'm okay.
那么糟吗      什么
Ooh. that bad huh?         What?
瑞秋 我可以感受到女人的忧伤脆弱
Look, Rach, I can sense when women are depressed and vulnerable.
这是我的天赋之一 坐下
It's one of my gifts. Sit.
噢
Oh!
乔伊 当我看到 他跟她一起走下飞机的那一刻
Joey, when I saw him get off that plane with her,
我真的以为我已经跌到谷底了
I really thought I just hit rock bottom.
可是今天的感觉就像 这是谷底
But today, it's like there's rock bottom,
然后下面还有50英尺的垃圾
50 feet of crap,
然后才是我
then me.
把你的感觉告诉罗斯
You gotta tell Ross how you feel.
我怎么能去对他说 那茱莉怎么办
Oh, come on, how can I just tell him? What about Julie?
她怎样
What about her?
他们在一起才两星期
They've only been going out for two weeks.
罗斯已经爱你快十年了
Ross has been in love with you for like 10 years.
我不知道 我不知道      瑞秋 瑞秋
I don't know. I don't know.         Look, Rach, Rach.
我交往过很多女人
I've been with my share of women.
其实我交往过很多很多女人
In fact, I've  been with a lot of people's share of women.
重点在于
But the point is
我对任何人的感觉 都不及罗斯对你的感情
I've never felt about anyone the way Ross felt about you.
真的
Really?
喂 老乡
Yo, paisan.
我可以跟你谈一下吗
Can I talk to you for a sec?
你的裁缝 是一个很坏的人
Your tailor is a very bad man!
法兰克 你在说什么啊
Frankie? What are you talking about?
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
乔伊的裁缝
Joey's tailor
占我便宜
took advantage of me.
什么      不可能
What?         No way.
我去他那里有12年了
I've been going to the guy for 12 years.
他说他要量我的内侧长度
Oh, come on. He said he was gonna do my inseam.
然后他就沿着我的腿往上摸 然后就很明显的
Then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite...
什么
What?
包住了
Cupping.
他们就是这样量裤子的
That's how they do pants!
首先 量一边 把它推到一旁
First they go up one side, they move it over.
再量另一边 把它推回来
Then they go up the other side, they move it back,
然后再量后面
then they do the rear.
干嘛 罗斯 告诉他
What? Ross, will tell him.
裁缝不都是这样量裤子的吗
Isn't that how a tailor measures pants?
对 是 没错 在牢里
Yes, yes, it is. In prison!
你有毛病啊
What's the matter with you?
干嘛啦
What?
不是那样子的吗
That's not?
哦 我的天
Oh my God.
即使是玛丽泰勒摩尔的发型 都比我的好看
Even Mary Tyler Moore would've been better.
我喜欢这发型
Well, I like it.
真的 我觉得这是十全十美
Yeah I do. I think it's a 10!
谢谢你
Thank you.
我的头发很让人开怀
My hair is very amused.
得了 这也不是最惨的事
Oh, come on, Monica, things could be worse.
我是说 你可能会被"困在纽约月光中
I mean, you could "get caught between the moon and New York City".
我知道很疯狂 不过千真万确 (电影主题曲歌词)
I know its crazy, but it's true."
真多谢
Thank you.
嗯 我得走了 再见      待会儿见
Well, I gotta go. Bye.         See you.
再见 瑞秋
Bye, Rach!
等等 你要走了吗
Oh, wait, are you leaving?
对呀 所以我才说再见
Yeah, that's kinda what I meant by "bye".
我可以跟你谈一下下吗      好
Well, can I talk to you for a sec?        Okay.
嘿 医生做疝气检查的时候
Hey, when the doctor does that hernia test...
那是可以的
That's okay.
有什么事吗      嗯
What's going on?         Hmm...
首先      嗯
Well, okay, first of all...         Mmhm.
巴洛和我并没有复合
Paolo and I are not back together.
那只是我干的一件傻事
That was a stupid thing that I did.
如果我能使时光倒转
And if I could go back in time and do it again,
我绝对不会这么做
well I wouldn't.
其次呢
Second of all,
干嘛
What?
好吧
Okay.
说话前 我想先问清楚
Before I say anything, I just need to know.
这是不是又是你与男友分手
Is this one of those things where you break up with a guy.
我告诉你我的想法
And then I tell you what I think.
然后第二天你们又重修旧好
And the next day you get back together with the guy.
然后我就变成一个大傻瓜        不是
And I look like a complete idiot?         No, no, no.
好吧 好 那么 我觉得那家伙是个大浑蛋
Okay. Well, then, I think the guy's scum.
我讨厌他 我真的 真的很恨他
I hate him. I mean, I actually, I physically hate him.
我一直是这种感觉
You know? I always have.
你值得一个比他更好的男人
And you are way too good to be with a guy like that.
真的
Really?
瑞秋 你值得一个能欣赏你的男人
Rach, you deserve to be with someone who appreciates you
一个能了解你的 风趣 甜美 温柔
and who gets how funny and sweet and amazing...
可爱和性感的男人
and adorable and sexy you are.
你知道吗 就是一个每天早上醒来都会想
You know? Someone who wakes up every morning thinking,
哦 我的天 我跟瑞秋在一起
"Oh my God. I'm with Rachel!"
知道吗 就是一个让你感觉非常好的人
You know? Someone who makes you feel good.
就像我对茱莉的感觉一样
Like the way I do with Julie.
还有什么话吗
Was there a "second of all"?
没有了 我想就这些了
No. I'm... I think that was the whole "all".
我得走了      好
I gotta go.         Yeah.
好吗 好      谢谢
Okay? Okay!         Thanks.
好
Okay.
不 我对天发誓 老爸
No, I swear to God, Dad!
别人不是那样量裤子的
That's not how they measure pants!
我想剪个较短的发型
I was thinking of doing it shorter.
就像安蒂麦道威尔那样
You know, like Andie MacDowell's new haircut.
可以 我会剪      真的
Oh, yeah. Oh, I could do that.         Really?
没问题 你要现在就剪吗      太棒了
Yeah. Do you wanna do it right now?         Great!
好啊      好啊
Okay         Okay
再见
See you.
好吧 这次我想要非常确定
Okay, I just wanna make really sure this time.
安蒂麦道威尔是
Andie MacDowell is the girl
"四个婚礼一个葬礼"里的那个女的 对吧
from "Four Weddings and a Funeral", right?
不是
No.
不是 那是洛帝麦道威尔
No, no, no, no, no, no. That's Roddy McDowaII.
安蒂麦道威尔是 "人猿星球"里的那个家伙
Andie MacDowell is the guy from "Planet of the Apes".
噢 对哦 谢谢      不客气
Oh! Yeah, okay. Thank you.         You're welcome.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧